Idol at night
Come on! And the third one is...
Heavy?
I mean, heavy is...
Is this heavy?
It's heavy. This is heavy love,
Heavy love.
Of course, I love my guesses, but I also love the fans and the members,
I am told by both fans and members that my love is very heavy.
But I am not really aware of it,
I see the members everyday,
I see the members everyday, but when I go back to their LINEs...,
Do you like me? I see them every day,
How much do you like me? I send them a lot of cute comments,
I'm so cute. I'm... I'm...
I didn't notice it at all.
That's a line between you and the members, isn't it?
That's right. During the talk show the other day,
I was asked to go back to the members' LINE conversations from years ago,
I told the members that I loved them,
I never said anything like that, but does that mean you like me? I was sending them so many messages,
I was sending them so many messages,
At that time, I felt that it was indeed a bad idea,
That kind of thing happened on a daily basis,
I was told by many of my fans that I was very heavy,
I thought, "My feelings are too heavy,
But that's all right now.
But now I'm fine with it.
How do you feel about your fans?
I want my fans to love me too,
I see.
I'm the type of person who wants something in return. I'm the kind of person who wants something in return.
Rather than unconditional love, I want them to love me back.
Give it back.
I want you to return it, and you've come to love me a lot,
I have a lot of fans who say that they love me,
But I want you to say something,
If you don't say something like that, I won't understand.
So, I want to hear "I love you" or "I love you,
I want you to tell me that you love me, that you like me, that you love me, that you love me, that there is no one else but Yugetsu,
That's how I do it,
I don't really think of myself as heavy,
I don't think of myself as a heavy person, but I don't think of myself as a heavy person,
Fans can participate in the game and communicate with each other in the game.
I send them a gift,
I send a gift, and everyone says, "Omo thank you very much.
When I send a gift, everyone says, "Omo thank you.
Omo" is the word,
It has become common among Yutsuki's fans recently.
At first, it was quite scary,
But now we are taking a step forward,
But we are taking it one step further.
We have been able to nurture them more and more,
Students are becoming more and more..,
Daikoku-san's fans.
I'm so happy to see that.
So, I've been saying that I don't understand unless you put it into words,
The first statement of the benefit session starts with "I love you.
They are amazing people, aren't they?
Yes, they are.
The team in the game is Yabba Leader and Yabba Tomo,
Yabba Leader and Yabba Tomo.
It fits perfectly.
I also love Yabba Tomo and his friends, and I go to bed with them.
They are Yabba Tomo.
It's wonderful.
So our bond is deepening.
Well, it's wonderful.
I learned a lot.
Thank you very much.
The third element is,
The third element was "Omo!
I'm so glad you enjoyed it.
Not even for one more second, please finish your bath.
That's what I mean.
Yabasan no yabaotomo yabadorisensan a-san
I got a big kick out of the "tsunsu-san's" statement!